He sprang to his sleigh To his team gave a whistle
他拉起他的雪橇 他吹起他的口哨
And away they all flew Like the down of a thistle
他們奔馳而去 如同薊草的細毛
But I heard him exclaim Ere he drove out of sight
但我聽他喊出 就在他要消失飛去之前
"Merry Christmas to all And to all a good night."
「祝大家聖誕快樂 還有大家有個美好的夜晚」
Wow! That was great! You really wrote that?
哇！真是太棒了！ 真的是你自己創作的嗎？
Say goodbye, elves. I'm off to Tulsa.
再見了，精靈們 我要去土爾沙了
I can't believe you won't be here for Christmas.
我不敢相信聖誕節你竟然會不在這裡
You're really not coming back?
你真的不回來嗎？
We have this paperwork that needs to be filed by the end of the year.
我們有很多報告都要 在年底的時候歸檔
Why can't those dumb Tulsa people do the work?
為什麼那些愚蠢的土爾沙人 沒有辦法做呢？
Because those dumb people got everything dumped on them..
因為那些愚蠢的人 得接收了一切…
by the arrogant jerks in the New York office.
王八蛋紐約人丟給他們的工作
I'm caught between two worlds.
我被卡在兩個世界中間
- If I don't get it done, I'll be fired. - It's so unfair.
-如果我不去做，我就會被炒魷魚 -真是不公平
- You don't even like your job. - So. Who does?
-你根本就不喜歡你的工作 -那又如何呢，誰喜歡自己的工作？
- I like my job. - I love my job.
-我喜歡我的 -我愛我的工作
- I can't wait to go back to work. - I can't get enough dinosaurs.
-我等不及要回去上班了 -我對恐龍就是玩不厭
I'm sorry I won't be here.
我很抱歉沒有辦法回來
It's hard enough not seeing you during the week..
平常沒有辦法見到你已經夠難受了…
but for Christmas..
但是聖誕節…
If this is what you have to do, I understand.
如果這就是你必須要做的事 我會諒解
Thanks.
謝謝
I'll see you New Year's Day.
新年當天見
You're not gonna be here New Year's Eve?
你除夕沒有要回來嗎？
- Did I not mention that? - No.
-我沒有提過嗎？ -沒有
And to all a good night!
那大家晚安了！
The One With Christmas In Tulsa
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
All right, everybody. I know it is Christmas Eve..
好了大家，我知道今晚是聖誕夜…
and you'd rather be with family, but there is no call for writing..
你們都想要跟家人在一起 但是也不可以寫…
"Screw you, Mr. Bing" on the back of my chair.
「去你的，賓先生」 貼在我的椅子後面
By the way, you can all call me Chandler.
對了，你們叫我錢德就可以了
- Hey. - Hey. Where you been?
-嘿 -嘿，你跑哪去了？
I was checking out that insurance company's Christmas party on three.
我去三樓看那間保險公司的聖誕派對
It was really beautiful. They have decorations and this huge tree.
真的是很美，他們有很多裝飾品 還有一顆很大的樹
And I just thought, to hell with them, we have to work.
然後我就想，去他們的 我們竟然要工作
So I stole their ham.
所以我偷了他們的火腿
Hear that? You may not be with your families..
聽到了沒？ 你們或許沒有跟家人在一起…
but at least it's gonna smell like ham in here.
但是至少這裡也可以 聞到過節的火腿味
My kid's in a play right now.
我的小孩現在正在表演話劇
You know what? I know what will cheer you up.
你們知道嗎？我知道要怎麼鼓舞你們
I had a talk with the boys in New York. I told them about all your hard work..
我跟紐約那邊的人談過了 我告訴他們你們全是如何辛勤工作…
and that a little Christmas bonus may be in order.
所以你們可能都會 得到一些聖誕獎金
"A donation has been made in your name to the New York City Ballet."
已經以您的名義把一項捐款…
捐贈給紐約市立芭蕾舞團
Well, that's like money in your pocket.
嗯，那其實就像是 進了你們的口袋一樣啊？
All right, you want me to say it? This sucks.
好了，你們一定要逼我說嗎？ 這實在很爛
Being here sucks. This work sucks!
在這裡真是爛，這份工作真是爛！
Now it feels like Christmas.
現在就有點像是聖誕節了
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
At least you get to go home and be with your families tonight.
至少今晚你們都還可以 回家跟家人在一起
I have to go to an empty hotel room and lay down..
我只能回去一間空蕩蕩的旅館房間 然後躺在…
on a very questionable bedspread.
一張很有衛生問題的床單上
Then tomorrow, you get to have Christmas in your own houses.
然後明天，你們都可以 在自己家裡過節
Which, by the way, none of you have invited me to.
順便提一下，你們沒有一個邀請我去
- You can come to my house. - No, thanks.
-你可以來我家 -不用了，謝謝
- It was a nice pep talk. - Thanks.
-真是精彩的精神講話 -謝謝
I'm actually thinking about becoming a motivational speaker.
我是真的有在想要成為激勵演說家
So if you were home right now, what would you be doing?
那如果你現在在家 你會是在做什麼呢？
Typical Christmassy stuff, you know. Our holidays are pretty traditional.
一般的聖誕節活動，你知道的 我們過節的方式是很傳統的
So here's a very special holiday song..
有一首十分特殊的節慶歌曲…
that I wrote for some very important people to me.
是我為一些對我很重要的人寫的：
Happy holidays, everybody.
大家聖誕快樂
Phoebe, look in the kitchen. I'll look in the back closet.
菲比，去檢查廚房，我去看衣櫥後面
I can save you time, ladies. I'm right here.
我可以節省你們的時間，女士們 我就正在這裡
Yeah. Chandler, why don't you take a walk.
錢德，你何不出去一下
This doesn't concern you.
這跟你沒有關係
We are looking for our Christmas presents from Monica.
我們在找摩妮卡準備的聖誕禮物
- What? That's terrible. - No, no. We do it every year.
-什麼？這實在太過分了 -不不，我們每年都這樣做的
Well, that makes it not terrible.
喔，那就樣就不過分了
No. Yeah, we never find them. She's always bested us, that wily..
是啊，我們從來沒有找到過 她總是高明過我們，那個狡猾又…
minx.
邪惡的女人
We're gonna search here for an hour..
我們會在這邊找一個小時…
and then we'll go to Joey's and search. Okay?
然後再過去喬伊家找，好嗎？
No, not okay. You can't look for Monica's presents.
不，不好 你們不可以找摩妮卡的禮物
- No, we have to. - No, you don't have to.
-我們一定要 -不，你們不需要這樣
And you can't, because I live here too.
你們不行，因為我也住在這裡
- Well, then you should look with us. - Why?
-那麼你應該幫我們找 -為什麼？
Aren't you worried about what to get Monica for Christmas?
你難道不煩惱要買什麼 聖誕禮物給摩妮卡嗎？
No, I have a great idea for a present for her.
不擔心，我已想好一個 很棒的禮物要給她
That's it? "A great idea"?
就這樣？「已經想好」？
That's not enough. What if she gets you a great present..
那是不夠的 萬一她送你的是一個很棒的禮物…
two medium presents and lots of little presents..
兩個中等的禮物 還有很多的小禮物…
and you got her one great present? That's gonna make her feel bad.
而你只送她一個很棒的禮物？ 那會讓她很傷心的
Why would you do that to her? Why? Why?
你為什麼要那樣對待她呢？ 為什麼？為什麼？
- If I helped, we could find them faster! - Right.
-如果我幫忙，我們就可以更快找到！ -沒錯
- We have a live one! - It's a Macy's bag!
-我找到一個了！！ -這是梅西百貨的袋子！
Who's it for?
這是要給誰的？
"Dear Losers: Do you really think I'd hide presents under the couch?
親愛的失敗者：你們真的認為 我會將禮物藏在沙發下面嗎？
P.S. Chandler, I knew they'd break you."
附註：錢德，我就知道 她們可以說服你
Rach, these are for you.
瑞秋，這些是給你的
Wiper blades. I don't even have a car.
雨刷，但是我根本就沒有車子
No, but with this new-car smell, you'll think you do.
是沒有，但是加上這個有 新車味道的芳香劑，你會以為你有的
Okay, Phoebe, your turn.
好了，菲比，輪到你了
Toilet seat covers!
馬桶座蓋紙！
Is that what you were doing while I was getting gas?
這是不是在我想放屁的時候 你們去弄的呢？
You guys.
你們倆
And for Ross, Mr. Sweet Tooth.
還有給羅斯，甜食先生
- You got me a cola drink? - And.. a lemon-lime!
-你們送我可樂？？ -還有…檸檬口味！
Well, this.. This is too much.
喔，這… 這禮真是太大了
I feel like I should get you another sweater.
我覺得我應該再送你一件毛衣
And last but not least..
最後一位…
They're ribbed, for your pleasure.
是羅紋保險套，讓你得到絕頂滿足
Well, hey, Ben?
嘿！班
What if the Holiday Armadillo told you all about the Festival of Lights?
要不要節慶穿山甲來告訴你 光明節的由來呢？
Cool!
好啊！
Come on, Ben.
來吧，班
Years and years ago, there were these people called the Maccabees!
很多年以前，有一群叫做 馬加比家族的人…
Merry Christmas!
聖誕快樂！
Santa!
聖誕老公公！
What are you doing here, Santa?
你在這裡做什麼呢？聖誕老公公
Well, I'm here to see my old buddy Ben.
喔，我是來看我的老朋友班的
What are you doing here..
你在這裡做什麼呢？你這只…
weird turtle-man?
奇怪的烏龜男？
I'm the Holiday Armadillo, your part-Jewish friend.
我是節慶穿山甲，你的 半猶太血統朋友
You sent me here to give Ben some presents.
你要我過來送些禮物給班的
Remember?
記得嗎？
What?
什麼？
Ben, why don't you open some more presents.
班，你何不去打開更多的禮物
Santa, the armadillo and I will have a talk in the kitchen.
聖誕老公公、穿山甲跟我要去廚房談談
There's a sentence I never thought I'd say.
我說了我以為這輩子 都認為不可能說的話
What are you doing?
你在做什麼呢？
You called and said you had trouble finding a Santa costume..
你打電話告訴大家 說你找不到聖誕老公公的服裝…
so I borrowed one from a guy at work.
所以我跟公司的同事借了這一套
Thank you, but you gotta leave.
謝謝你，但是你得要離開
- Why? - Because..
-為什麼？ -因為…
I'm finally getting him excited about Hanukkah.
我終於讓他對猶太光明節有興趣了
And you're wrecking it.
而你破壞了這一切
But I didn't get to shake my belly like a bowl full of jelly.
但是我還沒有機會把肚子 像果凍一樣搖的晃來晃去
I'm sorry, Chandler, but this is really important to me.
我很抱歉，錢德 但是這對我真的很重要
Okay, fine. I'll give the suit back.
好的，沒關係，我去還這套衣服
Hey, you think you can keep it another night?
嘿，你覺得可以把 這套衣服多留一晚嗎？
Santa? Really?
聖誕老公公？真的嗎？
- Yeah, is that okay? - Did your dad ever dress up like Santa?
-是啊，可以嗎？ -你爸爸有扮過聖誕老公公嗎？
- No. - Then it's okay!
-沒有 -那就沒問題了！
You know what, everybody?
你們知道嗎？你們大家
Go home. You should be with your families.
回家去，你們應該跟家人在一起
It's bad enough we're working New Year's Eve.
我們要在除夕夜工作就已經夠糟了
Did I not tell anyone about New Year's Eve?
我沒有告訴大家除夕夜的事嗎？
All right, look, go. Go home, okay? Merry Christmas.
好了，聽著，回去，回家去，好嗎？ 聖誕快樂
- Merry Christmas. - Peace on earth.
-聖誕快樂 -世界和平
- Bye. - Good. Godspeed, good people.
-再見 -很好，快走，一群好人
- You're not gonna go? - No. I couldn't leave you alone.
-你沒有要走嗎？ -沒有，我不能留你一個人在這裡
Thanks.
謝謝
Besides, I can't leave until that Christmas party downstairs clears out.
除此之外，我得要等到樓下的派對 都結束了我才能走
There are some pissed-off insurance people looking for that ham.
有一些氣爆了的保險員 正在找他們的火腿
- Chandler Bing. - Hi, honey. We're all here.
-錢德賓 -嗨，親愛的，我們全部都在這裡
We want to wish you a merry Christmas.
我們想要祝你聖誕快樂
- Merry Christmas! - Merry Christmas!
-聖誕快樂！ -聖誕快樂！
Merry Christmas. I miss you guys.
聖誕快樂，我想念你們
So is it horrible? Is everybody working really hard?
很難受嗎？每個人都在認真工作嗎？
Well, no, it's just me and Wendy.
嗯，沒有，只有我跟溫蒂
Wendy? That sounds like a girl's name.
溫蒂？聽起來想是女生的名字
It is. Did I not tell you about her?
就是女生，我沒有提過她嗎？
About the time you told me about New Year's Eve.
應該就在你跟我提起 除夕夜的事的時候
- Where's everybody else? - I sent them home.
-大家去哪了？ -我讓他們回家了
You are such a good boss. Is she pretty?
你真是好老闆，她漂亮嗎？
Answer faster. Answer faster.
快點回答，快點回答
- I don't know. - Answer better. Answer better.
-我不知道 -回答高明點，回答高明點
I don't think of her that way. I mean, she's a colleague.
我沒有那樣想過她 我是說，她是我同事
- What does she do there? - She's regional vice president.
-她在那邊是做什麼的？ -她是區域副總
- She's just below me. - She did what?
-她在我下面 -她什麼？
Below me.
她的職務在我下面
Wait, is Wendy the runner-up Miss Oklahoma?
等一下，溫蒂是那個 奧克拉荷馬小姐選美第二名嗎？
What?!
什麼！
Well, she didn't win.
嗯，她又沒有贏得后冠
All right, maybe I should let you..
好了，或許我應該讓你…
and the second prettiest girl in Oklahoma get back to work.
跟奧克拉荷馬第二漂亮 的女生回去工作了
Second prettiest that year. Of all the girls in Oklahoma, she's probably..
那一年第二漂亮的，以奧克拉荷馬 全部的女生來說，她或許…
Chandler, stop talking.
錢德，快閉嘴
Honey, there's really nothing to worry about.
親愛的，根本沒有什麼需要擔心的
- Okay. - I'm serious.
-好的 -我是說真的
Okay.
好的
- Merry Christmas. - Merry Christmas.
-聖誕快樂 -聖誕快樂
- Merry Christmas, you guys. - Merry Christmas.
-你們大家聖誕快樂 -聖誕快樂
- The wife says hi. - Fun conversation?
-我老婆打招呼 -談得愉快嗎？
Well, she's just got this weird idea that..
嗯，她有一種奇怪的想法 認為…
because you and I are alone something's gonna happen.
因為我們兩個單獨在一起 所以有事情會發生
Really?
真的嗎？
Would that be so terrible?
那樣很糟糕嗎？
This is probably the wrong thing to be worrying about..
我或許擔心得不對…
but you're getting ham on my only tie.
但是你把火腿沾上我唯一的領帶了
- Back off, missy! - Missy?
-走開，小妞！ -小妞？
I don't know. I'm not used to girls making passes at me.
我不知道，我不習慣女孩子 對我採取行動
Wait a minute. Am I sexy in Oklahoma?
等一下，我在奧克拉荷馬 算是性感的嗎？
- You are to me. - No. No. No!
-你對我是的 -不不，不！
- Look, I'm married. - So? I'm married.
-聽著，我已經結婚了 -那又如何？我也結婚了
I'm happily married.
我的婚姻很幸福
What's that like?
那是什麼樣的感覺呢？
- Right. So I'm sorry, but.. - Seriously? Happily married?
-是的，所以我很抱歉，但是… -真的？婚姻很幸福？
So that phone call before, that was happy?
所以剛才那通電話叫做幸福？
Well, look, it's not easy to spend this much time apart.
你知道，長期分開是很不容易的
She's entitled to be a little paranoid.
她是有資格有點神經質的…
Or, in this case, right on the money.
而且針對這件事 她猜對了
You know, she's amazing and beautiful and smart.
她很好、漂亮又聰明…
And if she were here right now, she'd kick your ass.
而且如果她現在在這裡 她一定會海扁你一頓的
Look, you're a really nice person, ham-stealing and adultery aside.
聽著，你是個很好人 除了會偷火腿跟偷腥之外
But what I have with my wife is pretty great.
但是我跟我老婆的感情很好
So nothing's ever gonna happen between us.
所以我們之間是不可能的
Okay, let me ask you something.
好的，讓我問你一件事
If what you and your wife have is so great..
如果你跟你老婆感情很好…
then why are you spending Christmas with me?
那你怎麼會跟我一起過聖誕節呢？
You were the most beautiful woman in the room tonight.
今晚你是這屋子裡最漂亮的女人
- Really? - Are you kidding?
-真的嗎？ -你不相信嗎？
You're the most beautiful woman in most rooms.
在大部分的屋子裡 你都是最漂亮的女人
What's going on? You and I just made out.
這是怎麼回事？ 我們剛剛親吻了
- You and I are making out? - Well, not anymore.
-我們在親吻？ -嗯，以後不會有了
- But we don't do that. - I know. I just thought it would be fun.
-但是我們倆從來不會那樣的 -我知道，我只是覺得那可能會很好玩
- How drunk are you? - Drunk enough that I wanna do this.
-你有多醉呢？ -我醉到讓我想要這樣做…
Not so drunk that you should feel guilty about taking advantage.
但又沒有醉到讓你覺得 佔我便宜是有罪惡感的
That's a perfect amount.
真是醉到恰到好處
- You know what's weird? - What?
-你知道什麼很奇怪嗎？ -什麼？
- This doesn't feel weird. - I know.
-就是這感覺一點都不怪 -我知道
- You're a really good kisser. - Well, I have kissed over four women.
-你真是接吻高手 -嗯，我吻過超過四個女人
You wanna get under the covers? Okay.
你想要到棉被底下嗎？
Wow, you are really fast.
哇，你真快
It bodes well for me that speed impresses you.
速度會得到你的讚賞 對我來說是好兆頭
- We're gonna see each other naked. - Yep.
-我們將要看到彼此裸體了 -是的
- You want to do it at the same time? - Count of three?
-你想要一起看嗎？ -數到三？
- One. - Two.
-一 -二
Three.
三
Well, I think it's safe to say that our friendship is effectively ruined.
我想我可以很肯定的說 我們的友情已經完全被摧毀了
We weren't that close anyway.
反正我們本來也沒有很好
Are you really gonna go out with that nurse-man?
你真的要跟那個男護士出去嗎？
Well, you and I are just goofing around.
嗯，反正你跟我只是玩玩而已
I thought, why not just goof around with him?
所以我想，我也可以跟他玩玩
I don't know if you've ever looked up "goofing around" in the dictionary.
我不知道你有沒有查過字典 「玩玩」是什麼意思
Well, I have.
我有查過…
And the technical definition is two friends..
專業的解釋就是兩個朋友…
who care a lot about each other and have amazing sex..
很在乎彼此 然後又做了很棒的愛…
and just want to spend more time together.
而且想要花更多的時間在一起
If you have this newfangled dictionary that gets you mad at me..
如果你那新版的字典 讓你對我生氣…
then we have to, you know, get you my original dictionary.
那我們就只好幫你買 我這本原版的字典
I am so bad at this.
我真是不會說話
I think you're better than you think you are.
我認為你比你想的還棒
- Really? Okay. So if..? - Know when to stop.
-真的嗎？好的，所以如果…？ -知道什麼時候該停
I sensed that I should stop.
我感覺到我應該停了
- So we're okay? - Yeah.
-所以我們沒事了嗎？ -是的
- Don't do the dance. - Right.
-別跳那個舞 -好的
I can't get married without something old, something new..
我沒有什麼舊的、什麼新的 什麼借來的、什麼藍色的…
- something borrowed, something blue. - Okay, okay.
-就沒有辦法結婚（美國習俗） -好的，好的
Here's something blue and new.
這是藍色的，而且是新的
You are so efficient. I love you.
你真是有效率，我愛你
- Let's go. - No, no, wait!
-我們走吧 -不不，等一下
We need something old.
我們需要什麼舊的東西
Okay. I have a condom in my wallet that I've had since I was 12.
好的，我有個保險套 我從十二歲就放在錢包裡了
That'll work!
那就可以拿來用了！
I don't think so.
我可不認為
Okay. Now we just need something borrowed.
好了，現在我們需要一個借來的東西
- Here, just take this. - That's stealing.
-這個，拿去 -這是偷竊的
We'll bring it back. Just put it under your dress.
我們會歸還的，塞到你洋裝裡
Okay, one thing at a time.
好了，事情一件一件照步驟來
Listen..
聽著…
I've been thinking.
我一直在想
It's not fair for me to ask you to spend all of your money on our wedding.
我要求把你所有的積蓄花在 我們的婚禮上，是很不公平的事
I mean, you work.. You work really hard for that.
我是說，你工作… 你辛苦工作才存到的
- Well.. - Well, you work for that.
-嗯… -好了，工作存到的
Look, I've thought about it too. And..
聽著，我也有想過，而且…
I'm sorry. I think we should spend all of the money on the wedding.
我很抱歉 我想我們應該將所有錢花在婚禮上
- You do? - Yeah. I'm putting my foot down.
-你真的覺得嗎？ -是的，我徹底的想清楚了…
Yeah, look, when I proposed..
聽著，當我求婚的時候…
I told you that I would do anything to make you happy.
我告訴你我會盡一切能力讓你快樂
And if having the perfect wedding makes you happy, then..
而如果一個完美的婚禮 能夠讓你快樂，那麼…
Then that's what we're gonna do.
那就是我們必須要做的是
You are so sweet.
你真的好貼心
But wait. What about our..? What about the future and stuff?
但是等一下，那我們…？ 那我們將來的計劃呢？
Forget about the future and stuff. So we only have two kids.
管他什麼將來的計劃 我們只生兩個小孩就好了
You know, we'll pick our favorite, and that one will get to go to college.
然後我們再挑選我們喜歡的那一個 送他去念大學就好了
- You've thought about that? - Yeah.
-你有想過我們的將來嗎？ -有啊
- How many kids were we gonna have? - Four. A boy, twin girls..
-我們要生幾個小孩呢？ -四個，一個男生，雙胞胎女生…
and another boy.
然後再一個男生
- What else did you think about? - Well..
-你還有想過什麼呢？ -嗯…
stuff like where we'd live, you know.
像是我們要住的地方，你知道的
Like a small place outside the city where our kids could ride bikes and stuff.
在市中心外面的小房子 我們的孩子可以學習騎腳踏車
And we could have a cat that had a bell on its collar..
我們可以養隻貓，頸圈上有個鈴鐺…
and we could hear it every time it ran through the little kitty door.
然後每次它經過小貓咪門的時候 我們就可以聽到鈴鐺聲
We'd have an apartment over the garage where Joey could grow old.
我們會在車庫上面留一間房間 讓喬伊可以在那裡養老
You know what?
你知道嗎？
I don't.. I don't want a big, fancy wedding.
我不需要大型豪華的婚禮了
- Sure you do. - No.
-你當然需要 -不
I want everything that you've just said.
我想要你剛剛說的一切
I want a marriage.
我只想要結婚
You sure?
你確定嗎？
- I love you so much. - I love you.
-我好愛你 -我愛你
- I love it! - Really? You're not gonna return it?
-我太喜歡了！ -真的嗎？你不會拿回去退嗎？
Well, not this second.
嗯，不會馬上
Hey, look, you guys. It's snowing!
嘿，你們瞧，下雪了
- Wow, it's so beautiful. - Wow, it really is.
-哇，真漂亮 -哇，真的是
Wendy's a fat-girl name.
溫蒂是胖女生的名字
Aren't we done with that?
我們還沒有說夠嗎？
Okay, fine. Fine. Let's talk about snow.
好啦，不說了 我們來聊雪
Do you think it's snowing in Tulsa where my husband's having sex on a copier?
你們覺得我老公在影印機上面做愛的 那個土爾沙有在下雪嗎？
- Hey. - Oh, my God.
-嘿 -喔！我的天！
Look at that. That's a Christmas miracle!
瞧瞧這，這真是聖誕奇跡！
- What are you doing here? - I wanted to be with you.
-你在這裡做什麼呢？ -我想要跟你在一起
I missed you so much.
我好想你
- Hey, hey. Who'd you miss the most? - Monica.
-嘿，你最想念誰呢？ -摩妮卡
Gotcha.
知道了
- I never want to leave you again. - I thought if you left, you'd get fired.
-我再也不要離開你了 -我以為如果你走了會被炒魷魚的
Turns out they can't fire me. Because I quit.
他們沒有辦法炒我魷魚的 因為我不幹了
- What? - What? You..? You really quit your job?
-什麼？ -什麼？你？你真的辭職了？
Yeah. It was a stupid job, and I could not stand leaving you.
是的，那是份愚蠢的工作 而我無法忍受離開你
Why should I be the only one who doesn't do what he really wants to do?
我為什麼要當那個唯一 必須做他不想要做的事的人？
- Well, what do you really wanna do? - I have not thought this through.
-那你真的想做什麼呢？ -這件事我沒想清楚
- Oh, my God. - I know. I should've talked to you first.
-喔！我的天！ -我知道，我應該先跟你討論的
No, I think that this is what you wanna do. I think it's great!
不，我想如果這是你想要的 我認為這很棒！
Thanks.
謝謝
Chandler, your being here is the best Christmas present I could ever imagine.
錢德，你能夠在這裡 是我有過最棒的聖誕禮物了
- Now give me my real gift. - Yeah.
-現在給我真正的禮物 -好
- Thank you. - Here, pass those around.
-謝謝 -這裡，分給大家
"A donation has been made in your name to the New York City Ballet."
「一項捐款已經以您的名義 捐贈給紐約市立芭蕾舞團」
How did you know?
你怎麼會知道我要這個呢？
What? Are you kidding? I can't return this.
什麼？你在開玩笑嗎？ 我不能退還這個的
It's time we started thinking about other people.
該是我們關懷別人的時候了
And besides, this gift still says, "I love you guys."
除此之外，這份禮物還包含了 「我愛你們」
- Mine says, "To Lillian Myers." - I don't have a job.
-我的上面寫「給莉莉安邁爾」 -我可是失業了
Actuary? No.
精算師？不
Bookkeeper? No.
簿記員？不
Topless dancer?
上空舞者？
Hey, you know what I just realized? You are the sole wage earner.
嗨，你知道我剛剛才想通什麼嗎？ 你是家裡唯一收入來源
You are the head of the household. I don't do anything. I'm a kept man!
你是這個家的戶長 我什麼都沒做，我是被供養的小白臉！
You are.
沒錯
Honey, here's 20 bucks.
親愛的，這裡有二十塊
Go buy yourself something pretty while I'm at work tomorrow.
我明天去上班的時候 你去買一些漂亮的東西